Guide to the Publishers Weekly: Reference Files,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Reference Files, 1909-2007
  - PO, 1939-2005 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Pocket Books, Inc.
    - 1939-2005 (Box 55, Folder 1-4)
    - Avon Books Case, 1940-1944 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Comet Books; Pocket Books, Jrs., circa 1949-1953 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - History, 1931-1967, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Staff, 1939-2002 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Popular Library, 1947-1984 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Clarkson Potter, 1959-2003 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - PRA - PRO, 1962-2004, (2 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
  - Frederick A. Praeger, Inc., 1950-1999 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Byron Preiss, 1993-2004 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc.
    - 1941-2003, (3 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 6-8)
    - Staff, 1937-1994 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Primedia, Inc. (Formerly K-III Communications Corporation), 1989-2003, (2 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Primer Press, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Princeton University Press, 1919-2001, (3 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 4-6)
  - PRU - PY, 1951-2006 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Public Affairs, 1997-2005 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs Press, 1946-1979 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Pushcart Press, 1971-2001 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - George Palmer Putnam, Inc.
    - 1909-2005, (5 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 1-5)
    - History, 1910-1994 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Staff, 1950-1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Pyramid Publications, 1941-1982 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    (See Also: Jove/Harcourt Brace Jovanovich)
  - Q, 1947-2005 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - RA, 1949-2005 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - RA - RE, 1909-1949 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Rand McNally and Company
    - 1909-2003, (2 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    - Staff, 1952-1984 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Random House
    - 1951-1984, (4 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 6-9)
    - 1985-2003, (8 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 1-8)
    - 2003, (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - History, 1936-1995, (3 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 3-5)
    - Staff, 1939-2005, (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 6-7)
  - RE
    - 1934-2004 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - 1934-2004 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Reader's Digest Books/Reader's Digest Press, 1967-2006, (2 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
  - Reader's Digest Fund, 1991-2001 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Reed Publishing, 1985-1995 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Regan Books, 1995-2007 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Henry Regnery - See Contemporary Books
  - Regnery Gateway, 1977-2005 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Reilly and Lee, 1927-1970 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Reinhold Publishing Corporation, 1945-1975, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    (See: Van Nostrand)
  - Fleming H. Revell Company, 1938-1988 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Reynal and Company, 1933-1968 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    (See Also: Blue Ribbon Books)
  - RF - RL, 1915-1949 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - RG - RI, 1940-2005 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Rinehart and Company
    (See Also: Holt, Rinehart and Wintson)
    - 1918-1961 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - History, 1929-1960 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Staff, 1934-1981 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Rizzoli, 1964-2005 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - RM - RZ, 1909-1949, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Roberts - Ronald, 1921-2004 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Rodale, 1947-2006 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Marcel Rodd Company, Inc., 1944-1949 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Rosebud - Rutsky, 1932-2005, (2 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
  - Samuel Roth, 1927-1957 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Roy Publishers, 1939-1971 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - William E. Rudge, 1930-1931, Undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Rutgers University Press, 1941-1979, 1993-1995 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - SA - SE (Old), 1909-1971, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - SAA - SAN, 1915-2005 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - SAR - SBS, 1943-2001 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - St. Martin's Press
    - 1952-1987 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - 1988-2005, (2 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - Howard W. Sams and Company, 1958-1995 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    (See Also: Bobbs-Merrill Company)
  - W. B. Saunders Company, 1938-1991 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - SC, 1932-2005 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Schoken Books, 1946-2005 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Scholastic, Inc.
    - 1964-2006 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - 1964-2006, (2 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
  - Science Research Associates, 1943-1988 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Scott, Foresman and Company, 1932-1995, (2 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 4-5)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons
    - 1934-2006, (2 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 6-7)
    - History, circa 1916-1994 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Staff, 1915-1995, (2 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 2-3)
  - SE - SH, 1927-2004, (2 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
  - Seabury Press, 1952-1985 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - SF - SQ, 1909-1950 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Sheed and Ward, 1985, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Sierra Club Books, 1961-2002 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - SI - SM
    - 1938-2004 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - 1938-2004 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Simon and Schuster
    (See Also: Golden Books; Golden Press)
    - 1924-1995, (8 Folders) (Box 68, Folder 2-9)
    - 1991-2006, (5 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 1-5)
    - American Psycho, 1990-2000 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - History, 1924-1996, (2 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 7-8)
    - Staff, 1926-2001, (3 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
  - Skira, 1949-1967 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - William Sloane Associates, 1946-1969 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - SN - SO, 1946-2005, (2 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 6-7)
  - SP - SR, 1942-2005 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - ST
    - 1952-2005 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - 1952-2005 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - ST - SZ, 1909-1959 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Stackpole Books, 1936-1980 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University Press, 1928-2000 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Stein and Day, 1962-1994 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Sterling Publishers Company, 1952-2006 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - F.A. Stokes and Company
    - 1916-1950 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - History, 1910-1943 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Stone and Kimball, 1925-1939, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Lyle Stuart, 1958-1991 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - SU - SZ, 1920-2002 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Summit Books, 1977-1992 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Sunset Publishing Corporation, 1941-1993 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Syracuse University Press, 1945-1978, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - TA, 1909-2003 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - TBW - TE, 1945-2004 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - TF - TL, 1913-1919, 1948-2003 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Thomson Corporation, 1957-2006 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Thunder's Mouth Press, 1985-2004 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - TI - TO, 1946-2006 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Time, Inc./Time-Life Books
    - 1952-1978 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - 1979-1993 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Time Warner, Inc.
    - 1989-2006, (6 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 2-7)
    - 2000-2006, (2 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - Times Books (Formerly Quadrangle), 1977-2003 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    (See Also: Random House)
  - Times Mirror Company, 1960-2000, (3 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 4-6)
  - TR - TZ (Old), 1915-1958 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - TR - TZ, 1942-2005, (2 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 8-9)
  - Transatlantic Arts, Inc., 1943-1970 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Tribune Company, 1992-2001 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Turner Publishing, 1989-1997 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Ukrainian - Universe, 1942-2005, (2 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 4-5)
  - UM - UQ, 1909-1922, 1947-1949 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Frederick Ungar Publishing Company, 1940-1988 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Unicorn Press, 1943-1968 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - United Methodist Publishing House, 1914-1992, (3 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 9-11)
  - University A - Osborne, 1933-2003 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - University Books, Inc., 1936-1988 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - University Microfilms, 1932-1985 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    (Includes Edwards Brothers)
  - University Presses--A-Z, 1937-2004, (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 4-5)
  - University of California Press, 1933-2002 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1933-2003, (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 7-8)
  - University of Michigan Press, 1933-2005 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - University of Minnesota Press, 1938-2005 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - University of Nebraska Press, 1944-1993 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - University of New Mexico Press, 1941-1995 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - University of North Carolina Press, 1938-1997 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - University of Oklahoma Press, 1938-1982 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - University of Pennsylvania Press, 1933-1949 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - University of South Carolina Press, 1949-2000 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - University of Texas Press, 1950-1991 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - University of Washington Press, 1946-1990 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - University of Wisconsin Press, 1933-2004 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - V, 1940-2005 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Van Nostrand Reinhold, 1912-1997 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Vanguard Press, 1928-1990 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Veritas Press, Inc., 1939, 1945 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Paramount Communications/Viacom, 1993-2005, (3 Folders) (Box 78, Folder 2-4)
  - Viking Press/Penguin
    - 1932-1983 (Box 78, Folder 5-6)
    - 1984-2005 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
    - Staff, 1932-1992 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Villard Books, 1983-2000 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Vintage, 1954-2005 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Voyager Company, 1994-1996 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - WA - WE, 1910-1948 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - WA, 1939-2006, (2 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 8-9)
  - Walker and Company, 1961-2005 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Frederick Warne and Company, 1931-2002 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Warner Books/Warner Paperback Library, 1961-2007, (3 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
  - Ives Washburn, Inc., 1933-1977 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Franklin Watts, 1942-1995 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - WE, 1925-2004 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Webster Publishing Company, 1949-1965 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Wesleyan University Press, 1958-1993 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - West Publishing, 1933-2003 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Western Publishing, 1936-1996, (2 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
  - Westminster Press, 1910, 1932-2000 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - WF - WH, 1919-2004 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - WF - WL, 1911-1921 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Whitman Publishing Company, 1936-1998 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Whittle Communications, 1989-2002 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Whttlesey House, 1930-1962 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    (See Also: McGraw Hill)
  - WI - WN, 1933-2004 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - John Wiley and Sons
    - 1913-2005, (4 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 1-4)
    - Interscience Publishers, 1941-1973 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Williams and Wilkins Company, 1932-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 6-7)
  - H.W. Wilson Company, 1929-1997 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - John C. Winston Company, 1920-1961, (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 2-3)
    (See Also: Holt, Rinehart and Winston)
  - William H. Wise and Company, 1917-1966 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - WO - WZ, 1931-2005 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Workman Publishing, 1969-2005 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Helen and Kurt Wolff, 1942-1990 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - World Book Company, 1932-1998 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    (See Also: Harcourt, Brace and World, 1960-)
  - World Publishing Company
    (See: William Collins Publishers)
    - 1939-1960 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - 1961-1980 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Staff, 1933-1981 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - X-Y-Z, 1941-2005 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Xerox Corporation, 1972-2000 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Yale University Press, 1914-1965, (2 Folders) (Box 84, Folder 5-6)
  - Zagat, 1991-2004 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Ziff-Davis Publishing Company, 1942-2000 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    (See Also: A.S. Barnes and Company, Inc.)
  - Zondervan Corporation, 1931-2005 (Box 84, Folder 9)